(忆往昔)
找到你们了
There you are.
-真不该来这儿啊  小子们  -梅格
- You shouldn't have come here, boys. - Meg!
她是个恶魔  萨姆
She's a demon, Sam!
我们要上天堂了  小天使
We're goin' to heaven, Clarence.
你还能怎样啊  你个废物
So, what can you do, you impotent sap?
那该死的是个啥东西
What the hell was that thing?
-也许是个始祖  -始祖  就像是
- It may have been an alpha. - An alpha? Like --
就是其他怪物的起源
First one who spawned all the others.
这里面的学问可多着呢
There's tons of lore about it.
我们知道你在找炼狱
We know you're looking for purgatory.
-想告诉我们原因吗  -炼狱广袤无垠
- You want to tell us why? - Purgatory is vast,
但却未被充分利用  又与地狱毗邻
underutilized, and hell-adjacent,
而且我想要它
And I want it.
给我猎捕去
Bring me creatures.
越高级的越好
Aim high on the food chain, please.
-我们可不是你的雇员  -绝对是
- We ain't your employees. - Of course you are!
你不过就是个在十字路口晃悠的恶魔罢了
You're nothing but a punk-ass crossroads demon.
那是曾经了
Was a punk-ass crossroads demon.
如今  已是地狱之王了
Now? King of hell.
我动动小手指  就能让萨姆的灵魂归位
I snap my fingers, Sam gets his soul back.
或是再把他丢回牢笼里
Or I shove Sam right back in the hole.
(如今)
我说过了
I told you.
我完全不知道
I don't know anything about --
抱歉  但你那可人的外貌完全得不到任何怜悯
Sorry...But your exceptional good looks aren't gonna buy you any mercy.
建议你还是乖乖招了吧
I suggest you talk.
接下来该试试哪一个呢
What should we use next?
扩张器呢
Speculum?
还是来些新奇的呢
Something more exotic?
听着  那可是炼狱
Look, it's purgatory.
我只知道  我死后会去那里
All I know is, I go there when I die.
没法给你绘张地图
It's not like I can draw you a map.
我碰巧知道你就是可以
I happen to know you can.
你搞错了
You're wrong.
我的消息绝对可靠
My sources are unimpeachable.
你可是你们这类的始祖啊
You're the father of your entire species.
你休想用"很傻很天真"这套糊弄我
You're really not pulling off this dumb-blonde act.
希望你能感激我是有多么努力地去寻找...
I hope you appreciate just how much effort I've gone to
寻找能够真正伤害你的东西
to find something that can actually hurt you.
当然  代价就是牺牲了很多你的小辈变形怪
Yeah, my tinkering has cost several lesser shifters their lives.
这是铱
Iridium.
相当稀有
Rarer than hell.
这玩意儿真的超贵
Would have been cheaper to drop a castle on you.
但我想我们一致认可  值得的
But I think we all agree -- worth it.
那么
So...
要不你乖乖地坦白
You start talking
要不我就把你身上突出来的部分都切掉
or I start chopping off all the bits that stick out.
动手吧  伙计
You go ahead, mate.
看看它能不能让我开口
See if it makes me want to chat.
你说什么
What was that?
炼狱在哪儿
Purgatory's where?
你这畜生究竟打算怎样啊
What is it with you animals?!
我跟你提过这个监狱有个婴儿室吗
Did I tell you this prison has a nursery?
全是你的宝宝
All yours.
我知道你有多在意他们
I know how much you care about them.
你花了好几个月才让他们回到你的羽翼下
You've spent months gathering them to your bosom.
现在没那么不可一世了吧
Not so cocky now, are we?
找到炼狱对我来说无比重要
Finding purgatory's important to me.
给你五秒钟时间告诉我炼狱在哪儿
You have five seconds to tell me where it is.
否则  我会当着你的面将他们抽筋剥骨
After that, I'll filet them in front of you,
把他们的脊骨扔到你腿上
toss their spines in your lap.
四  三  二
Four, three, two --
把他们都杀了吧  我们会造出更多后代
Kill them all. We'll make more.
看来我脑袋搬家了
Guess I kind of lost my head.
[邪恶力量 第6季第10集]
你们迟到了
You're late.
交通真是糟透了
You know, traffic was a bitch.
一个法国狼人
One rugaru.
克劳力呢
Where's Crowley?
别人找妓女也要向你报告吗
Banging a hooker in a sweet spot called none of your business.
瞧瞧呀  萨姆  恶魔也想幽默一把
Look at that, Sam -- demon trying to be funny.
噢  原来他是在搞笑啊
Oh, is that what just happened?
晚安了  娇娃们
Night, girls.
等等  等等  别急着走
Wait, wait. Hold up, hold up.
我们还能见到克劳力么
Are we ever gonna see Crowley again,
还是他只是派他的客串恶魔来领他的猎物
or is he just gonna keep sending his demon extras to pick up his laundry?
抱歉  我知道你在说话
I'm sorry. I know you're speaking.
也看到你嘴唇在蠕动
I see your lips moving,
但我真没搞懂你在说啥
But I can't understand what you're saying
因为我不说你们的鸟语
'cause I don't speak little bitch.
我们过去可是猎杀恶魔的
Remember when we used to gank demons?
不  老弟  去他妈的  我受够了
No, man, screw it. I'm done.
-冷静  -我们一直在帮那该死的克劳力跑腿
- Calm down. - We have been going on these freakin' Crowley runs,
可这根本屁用没有
and it's not getting us anywhere.
-迪恩  -唯一真的有所变化的就是
- Dean  - I mean, the only thing that's really changed
我每天都觉得羞耻和无助
is now I need a daily rape shower.
好吧  你说得没错  那我们执行B计划吧
Okay, you're right. Let's go with plan "B."
噢对了  我们根本就没有
Oh, yeah. We don't have one.
想出其他办法之前  抱歉  老哥
So till we do, sorry, dude.
你就只能忍了
Stock up on soap-on-a-rope.
迪恩  如果你想让我的灵魂归位
Dean, if you want to get my soul back,
那我们就只能这么做了  明白吗
That's what we got to do, okay?
明白
Yeah.
你想要自己的灵魂回来吗
You even want it back?
我不是正在为克劳力效命吗
I'm working for Crowley, aren't I?
没错
Yeah, well,
谁知道他会不会信守承诺呢
who says he's gonna hold up his end, you know?
那可是克劳力
It is Crowley.
你想过吗
You ever think of that?
对吗
Right?
没聊天的心情了  你是想说这个吗
So I guess the moment's over. Is that what you're saying?
萨姆
Sam!
又怎么了
What now?
我看能回答你的人来了
I think I know who you can ask.
邪恶的婊子
Evil bitch.
继续拣姐爱听的说
Keep sweet-talking me,
事情绝对会峰回路转
this could go a whole new direction.
梅格  我可是想你想得不得了啊
Meg. I've been dying to see you again.
我这不是来了  小哥
Well, here I am, big boy.
那咱现在干点什么呢
So, what should we do now?
把你撕成碎片怎么样
How 'bout I rip you to shreds?
重口味  我喜欢
Kinky. I like.
不过不介意的话  我要先来问几个问题
But a little Q&A first, if you don't mind.
说  你们头儿在哪儿
Now, where's your boss?
你觉得我们会为别人卖命
You think we work for somebody?
我刚好知道了
I happen to know for a fact
你们在和克劳力的小恶魔们打交道
you've been juggling Crowley's orphans.
快说  他在哪儿
Now, where is he?
不知道  不在乎
Don't know, don't care.
你们已经为见他奔走了几个月了
But you been working his beat for months.
还没面圣的机会啊
Doesn't mean we get face time.
你们为他抓的那些始祖们他关在哪里
Where's he take all those things you snatch up for him?
我用一根棒棒糖跟你赌
I bet you an all-day sucker
那就是他的老巢
that's where his majesty's holed up.
好了  前戏姐玩儿够了
Okay, officially over the foreplay.
满足我  不然我自己上了
Satisfy me, or I please myself.
有什么好笑的吗  萨姆
Something funny, Sam?
是啊  梅格
Yeah. Meg.
真的  但你哥我的处境可是...
Really? 'cause where I'm sittin' --
别担心  她不敢伤你
Don't worry. She can't do jack squat.
她已经自身难保了
She's totally screwed.
萨姆  帮倒忙呢啊
Sam, not helping!
你看她  迪恩  她已经气疯了
Look at her, Dean. She's furious.
她要是能杀你  早动手了
If she could kill you, she'd have done it by now.
她在逃命
She's running.
是吗
Am I?
看你们那焦躁不安的样儿  应该没错
Judging by the level of flop sweat on all of you, yeah.
就是说  你们在躲克劳力
Which means you're running from Crowley.
这就对了
Which makes sense.
克劳力要赶尽杀绝路西法所有的死忠
Crowley would want to hunt down all the Lucifer loyalists
现在他才是老大
now that he's big man on campus.
你怎么知道
How would you know?
换做是我也会这么做
It's what I'd do.
她不能杀我们
She can't kill us.
她需要我们帮她找到克劳力
She needs us to get her to Crowley
好亲手干掉他
so she can stick that knife in his neck.
不是他死就是她亡
It's him or her.
这样的话  我是巴望你俩都死翘翘
Well, I hope you both lose.
不过  你加油哈
But good luck.
你现在知道该怎么做了吧
So, you know what you got to do now, right?
我猜猜哈  你会告诉我的
Let me guess -- you're gonna tell me.
和我们合作
Work with us.
擦  啥
Whoa, what?
我们会把克劳力双手奉上
We'll hand you Crowley with a bow.
只要让我们跟你们一起去
On one condition -- we go with you,
而且你在把他砍成肉酱前
and you help us wring a little something out of him
要帮我们从他那弄到一样东西
before you hack him to bits.
-要什么  -这不重要
- What? - Doesn't matter.
重要的是  你能不能帮我们得偿所愿
Question is, can you get us what we need?
在地狱时  我可是阿拉斯泰尔的徒弟
I apprenticed under Alastair in hell,
和你哥哥一样
just like your brother.
迪恩你说  我能否让克劳力对我唯命是从
So, Dean, can I make Crowley do whatever I want?
她可以
Yeah, she can.
那么  成交
It's a deal, then.
和两个萌货合作
Hugs and puppies all around.
你不打算给我们松绑吗
You gonna untie us?
拜托
Please.
明明自己被绑得很爽  就别装了
Don't pretend you don't enjoy it.
想跟我玩亲亲吗
You gonna kiss me?
走吧
Come on.
你抽什么疯
What are you doing?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是  你抽什么风呐
I mean, what are you doing?!
迪恩  是你想要搞死克劳力
Dean, you wanted to screw over Crowley.
美梦成真了哦
Merry Christmas.
啥
What?
你又想跟恶魔合作了吗
You want to work with a demon again?
咱是暂时跟恶魔合作
We're working with demons now.
我这样做是为了不再跟他们纠缠不清
I'm doing this 'cause I want to stop.
埃伦和乔都是她杀的
She killed Ellen and Jo.
我知道  但你不能感情用事  迪恩
I know. But you can't look at this emotionally, dean.
-我们需要她  -需要个毛
- We need her. - The hell we do.
那小婊子得手后肯定先搞死我们
That little bitch is gonna screw us over so fast --
当然  所以我们才要先下手
Of course. Which is why we'll screw her first.
只要一完事  梅格和她手下
Meg and her little posse are dead
就死定了
the second we're done with them.
-前提是他们没先把我们杀掉  -他们不会
- Yeah, if they don't kill us. - They won't.
因为我们有护身符
'cause we're bringing insurance.
卡西迪奥
Castiel...
我们需要你
We need you.
很重要的事
It's important.
小卡
Cass...
我们找到了个东西
We found something.
是...是个金盒子
It -- it's this...Gold box.
纳粹似乎曾经寻找过这东西
Apparently, nazis were after it back in the day.
某人尝试打开  结果整张脸被熔化了
Someone tried to open it, and their face melted off.
我们觉得是...
We think it's, uh --
做好心理准备哈
ready for this? --
约柜
The ark of the covenant.
没错
Yeah.
-所以吧  -我来了  萨姆
- So -- I'm here, Sam.
盒子在哪
Where is the box?
你居然相信了  真不可思议
I can't believe you fell for that.
那是"夺宝奇兵"里的情节诶  小白痴
That was the plot of "Raiders," Idiot.
萨姆  我身陷战争之中
I'm mid-battle, Sam.
我才不想管
I could give a rat's ass
你和拉斐尔之间的狗屁较量
about your little pissing match with Raphael.
-萨姆  你听我说  -不  你听我说
- Listen to me, Sam --- No, you listen.
我不管你在天堂要面对的情况是什么
I don't care what you're dealing with up in heaven.
这是你欠我的
You owe me.
你可能不在乎  但是相信我
You may not care, but believe me --
抱歉  你觉得我们是来谈这个的吗
I'm sorry, do you think we're here to talk this out?
萨姆  我不能
Sam, I can't just --
如果你不帮我们
If you don't help us,
我会追捕你  然后杀了你
I will hunt you down and kill you.
是吗
Will you...
孩子
Boy?
怎样杀啊
How?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
不过我一定会找到方法的
But I will look until I find out,
别忘了我不睡觉
and I don't sleep.
萨姆  你需要帮助
You need help, Sam.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
你还真现身了啊
You actually showed.
萨姆  下次我请你吃鸡肉大餐
Wow. Sam, I owe you a chicken dinner.
发生了什么事
What happened?
没什么
No big.
这是朋友应该做的嘛
This is what friends do for each other.
这没用
It's not working.
克劳力在躲我
Crowley's hidden from me.
看来我们应该用强硬手段了
Well, looks like we're gonna have to try this the hard way.
有何贵干
Can I help you?
你们想干嘛
What do you want.
我们想知道克劳力在哪里
We want to know where Crowley is.
就算我知道  我凭什么要告诉你
If I even knew, why would I tell you?
因为你是我们的外公
'cause you're our grandfather.
萨穆埃尔  我会拿回我的灵魂
Samuel, I'm gonna get my soul back.
谁说你能拿回来
Who says you can get it back?
我
Me.
我很想帮忙  但是很抱歉
Look, I'd like to help, but I'm sorry.
这可是你外孙的灵魂
This is your grandson's soul.
我不能
I can't!
你到底怎么回事啊
What is wrong with you?
你心甘情愿替克劳力做事吗
You want to work for Crowley?
小卡  能让我们单独待会儿吗
Cass, can you give us a minute?
我们是你的血肉至亲
We're your blood.
但是如果你不想帮我们  我也不能逼你
But if you don't want to help us, I can't make you.
我就想知道为什么
But I just got to know why.
你有什么把柄在克劳力手上
What is Crowley holding over you?
你应该给我们说清楚吧
You owe us that.
妈妈
Mom?
他会把她带回来
He's gonna give her back to me.
克劳力要让妈妈起死回生吗
Crowley's gonna bring mom back from the dead?
是说你不想让她回来吗
You tell me you don't want her back.
你知道我们之间有个区别是什么吗
You know the one difference between us?
你的生活可以没有她
You know how to live without her.
我懂你的感受
Look, I know how you feel.
你懂个屁
No, you don't.
她是我女儿  她死了
She's my daughter, and she's dead.
但是我能让她活过来
And I can do something about it.
你真觉得克劳力会把她带回来吗
You really think Crowley's gonna make good here?
他把萨姆和我都带回来了
He brought Sam back! And me!
相信我  别走这条路
Trust me -- don't go down that road.
你说什么
What are you saying?
我说放弃吧
I'm saying stop trying.
这样一点好处都没有
It's gonna go nowhere good.
萨穆埃尔  我知道我们不一样
Samuel, I know we've had our differences,
但我是你的外孙
but I'm your grandson.
我告诉你
And I'm telling you
你这样做是大错特错
that this is wrong for so many reasons.
-你个伪君子  -我麻烦你吸取我们的教训
- You hypocrite. - I'm asking you to learn from our mistakes!
这种做法
Doing this --
每次都让我们被那群混蛋牵着鼻子走
this is how the bad guy gets us every time!
这是我们的致命弱点
It's our achilles heel!
显然我们一家人都这样
Apparently, it runs in the family.
我们会另想办法的
We will figure something else out.
好吗
Okay?
迪恩  对不起  但
I'm sorry, Dean, but --
好吧
Fine.
好吧  你把她带回来
Fine, you bring her back.
那你要怎么跟她说
But what are you gonna tell her, huh?
你告诉她  你和恶魔做了交易吗
You gonna tell her you made a deal with a demon?
-你不肯帮助她的儿子  -够了
- That you wouldn't help out her sons?! - That's enough!
出去
Just get out.
这个真复杂啊
It's very complex.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
如果这个送披萨的真的爱这位保姆
If the pizza man truly loves this babysitter...
他为什么一直打她屁股
...why does he keep slapping her rear?
可能她做了什么错事吧
Perhaps she's done something wrong.
你在看A片
You're watching porn?
为什么
Why?
电视里放的
It was there.
你不能当着很多男人的面看A片
You don't watch porn in a room full of dudes.
你也不能  谈论它
And you don't... talk about it.
快点关了
Just turn it off!
现在他鸡冻了
Well, now he's got a boner.
你们就干这些啊
Is this what you boys do?
和天使一起看A片
Sit around watching pornos with angels?
我不应该谈论这些的
I'm not supposed to talk about it.
萨穆埃尔  有何贵干
Why you here, Samuel?
玛丽也想我这么做
It's what Mary would want.
这些是我知道的事情
Now, this is what I know.
我们猎获的东西  都送到这里
Whatever we bag... ends up there.
他就在这里  折磨它们  审问它们
That's where he tortures them, interrogates them --
我不太清楚
I don't really know.
我没进去过  但那地方极其危险
Only been outside the place, but it's a death trap.
没有克劳力的允许  没人进得去
Nothing gets in that Crowley doesn't want in,
也没人出得来  就这样
and nothing gets out -- period.
谢了
Well, thanks.
我真希望你们不要走这条路
I wish you wouldn't do this.
和我们一起去吧
Come with us.
我是耳根子软  但还不想自杀
I may be soft, but I'm not suicidal.
记得我吗
Remember me?
我可记得你哦  小天使
I sure remember you, Clarence.
我们为何要跟这群下三滥的东西合作
Why are we working with these abominations?
我的肉身可喜欢你骂人的样子了
Keep talking dirty. It makes my meatsuit all dewy.
行了  都给我闭嘴
All right, simmer down.
我们知道克劳力在哪里
We know where Crowley is.
很好  说吧
Great. Do tell.
是啊  之后你再杀了我们跑路
Yeah, tell you so you can just leave us for dead.
你们哥几个的被弃妄想症挺严重
You boys have serious abandonment issues,
自己知道不
you know that?
我们带你去  可以吗
We'll show you, all right?
但我们得一起行动
But we're all going together.
我凭什么要相信你们
What, I'm just supposed to trust you?
不用  你没这么傻
No. You're not that stupid.
把刀给我下
Give me the knife for a minute.
不  我没这么傻
No. I'm not that stupid.
还想不想我们带你去找克劳力了
Do you want us to take you to Crowley or not?
你们都看到的
You saw him.
比起好好干活
He was more interested in killing us
他更想干掉我们
than getting the job done.
我只是为大家除掉个祸害
I just did all of us a favor!
慢着
Hey!
你就这么拿走了吗
You just gonna keep that?
本来就是我们的
You took this from us.
我不过是拿回自己的东西
I'm taking it back.
一小时后出发
We leave in one hour.
小卡  别杵在那儿发呆
You know, Cass, you could help.
我对我们的计划有点纠结
I'm ambivalent about what we're attempting.
勇闯恶魔老巢当然比不上
Well, breaking into monster gitmo
脱衣舞夜店的一对一服务
is not exactly a two-for-one in the champagne room.
我不确定找回萨姆的灵魂是不是明智
I'm not sure retrieving Sam's soul is wise.
等等  你说什么
Wait, what?
怎么了
Why?
我希望他能好好活着
I want him to survive.
你到底在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
萨姆的灵魂被困在牢笼里
Sam's soul has been locked in the cage
与米迦勒和路西法共处了一年多
with Michael and Lucifer for more than a year.
他们只能在他身上
And they have nothing to do
发泄怨气
but take their frustrations out on him.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
如果我们强行把那
If we try to force
残破的灵魂塞回萨姆的肉身
that mutilated thing down Sam's gullet,
我们无法预知后果会怎样
we have no idea what will happen.
-也许是毁灭性的  -你是说他会死
- It could be catastrophic. - You mean he dies.
我是说他会生不如死
I mean he doesn't.
麻痹瘫痪  精神错乱
Paralysis, insanity,
精神上的强烈痛苦
psychic pain so profound
会让他一辈子不得安宁
that he's locked inside himself for the rest of his life.
但你也说我们不能肯定
But you're saying you don't know anything for sure.
他还是有可能会没事
I mean, he could be fine.
-是有这可能  没错  -那就行了
- He could be, yes. - Okay, then.
但我严重怀疑这个可能性
But I sincerely doubt it.
那要是他有事  就由你来治好他
Well, if he's not fine, then you fix him.
迪恩  我无从下手
Dean, I wouldn't know where to begin.
你会有办法的  小卡  拜托
Then you figure it out, Cass! Come on.
现在的他只不过是具该死的躯壳
I mean, the guy's a friggin' replicant.
他需要自己的灵魂
He needs his soul.
我们把灵魂找回来
Look, we get it back.
如果到时有其他问题
And if there are complications,
我们再想办法处理
then we will figure out a way to deal with those, too.
这是自然
Of course.
如果我们失败了
Or we fail,
萨姆将承受非人的折磨
and Sam suffers horrifically.
太安静了
Seems pretty quiet.
并非如此  我感受得到
It's not. I can feel it.
在边门汇合
Meet me at the side door.
会不会有点太容易了
This all seem a little too easy to you?
的确
Way too easy.
有人吗
Is someone there?
求求你
Please.
求你救救我
Please help me.
你得救我出去
You got to get me out of here.
求你了  快救我出去
Please! You j-- you got to get me out of here!
走吧  迪恩
Come on, dean.
我们不能留在这
We got to move.
等等
Wait.
怎么了
What is it?
真该死  看门的来了
Damn it. Here come the guards.
地狱犬
Hellhounds.
跑
Go.
我就知道这是个陷阱
I knew this was a trap.
不然你想要什么  杯子蛋糕吗
What do you want, a cupcake?
这能挡它们一阵
All right, that should keep them out.
撑不了多久  有几条
Not for long. How many of them are there?
很多
Lots.
我精神上支持你们  姐这就去克利夫兰了
I'll be pulling for you... from Cleveland.
-什么  -我不知道事情会这样
- What?! - I didn't know this was gonna happen.
好在把我的肉身留给它们
Bright side -- them chewing up my meatsuit
能给你们赢点时间逃跑
ought to buy you a few seconds.
再见了
Seacrest out.
我想这是克劳力下的符咒
It's a spell, I think, from Crowley.
只要一进这房子  你就无法脱离肉身
Within these walls, you're locked inside your body.
报应啊  贱人
Karma's a bitch, bitch.
你要干什么
What are you gonna do,
你准备对着空气乱砍一通吗
you gonna slash thin air until you hit something?
你看得见它们
You can see them.
拿着  挡住它们  这是唯一的办法了
Take this. Hold them off. It's our best shot.
去找克劳力吧
At Crowley.
带着它去吧
Take it and go.
干掉那个伪善的贱货  我来挡住这些狗
You kill the smarmy dick. I'll hold off the dogs.
你要怎么做...
How are you gonna do that I--
这算什么
What was that?
我从批萨男那里学来的
I learned that from the pizza man.
水平一流哦
Well, a-plus for you.
我感觉浑身都被净化了
I feel so...clean.
好了  该走了
Okay, gotta go.
这玩意能对付得了地狱犬吗
Whoa, whoa, is that gonna work on a hellhound?
我们马上就能知道了  快走
Well, we're about to find out. Run!
我毛都看不到
I can't see Jack.
-小卡  -迪恩
- Cass?! - Dean.
你出卖了我们
You sold us out?
没错
Yes.
我得说...
And I have to say...
这是自迪克·切尼(布什任内的美国副总统)后我做过的最棒的交易
best purchase I've made since Dick Cheney.
好呀  克劳力
Hiya, Crowley.
最近如何
How's tricks?
你管不着
Above your pay grade.
一直在忙
Been working.
一件大事
Big things.
哎呀  不过到时你们已经死了  参加不了了
Alas, you'll be too dead to participate.
真的么
Really?
可惜我不得不干掉你们俩
Shame I have to do away with you both.
我还挺喜欢支使你们的呢
Rather enjoyed your indentured servitude.
萨姆
Sam?!
干嘛
Yeah?
我踩到一泡尿
I'm standing in pee.
就当你走运了吧
Consider yourself lucky.
呕
Yikes.
烂透了
That sucks.
你要是想告解  找牧师去吧
You want forgiveness, find a priest.
我只想让你理解我
I just want you to understand.
我太理解了...
Oh, I understand...
你就是个骗子
that you're a liar.
你口口声声血亲至上
You talk about putting blood first,
好笑的是  这和我老爸之前讲得差不多
which is funny 'cause you sound just like my dad.
不同的是  他的确就这么做了
Difference is, he actually did!
我就是血亲至上
I am putting blood first!
得了吧你
Oh, give me a break!
玛丽就是我的血脉  我的女儿
Mary's my blood! My daughter!
别跟我扯什么出卖不出卖  迪恩
Don't come at me like I sold you out, Dean.
你还出卖了你的亲生母亲
You sold out your own mother.
本来你可以选她还是萨姆
It was her or Sam,
你选了萨姆  就这么简单
and you chose Sam -- plain and simple.
你他妈扯淡
Oh, that is such crap!
你知道到底发生了什么吗
You want to know what really happened?
你选择了恶魔而不是你自己的外孙
You chose a demon over your own grandsons!
你爱怎么说随便
See it how you want.
我都不知道现在的萨姆是个什么东西
I don't even know what Sam is.
你还想让我保护他
And you want me to protect him?
至于你
And you?
你根本就是个陌生人
You're a stranger.
不  说真的  告诉我
No, really, tell me --
对我来说你到底算是个什么
what exactly are you supposed to be to me?
我来告诉你我算什么
I'll tell you who I am.
我是个你不想再看见的人
I'm the guy you never want to see again.
相信我  我一定会逃出去
'Cause I'll make it out of here. Trust me.
下一次你见到我
The next time you see me,
我会杀了你
I'll be there to kill you.
别以为还有什么下次了
Don't think there's gonna be a next time.
每天晚上你可都得小心
Whatever gets you through the night.
所以...
So...
克劳力想知道...
Crowley wants to know...
一切
Well, everything.
他让我好好招待你
Told me to carve it out of you.
你以为自己很爷们吗
Whatever makes you feel like a man.
你嘴上刻薄
You talk a mean game.
其实...
But, uh...
早就被吓坏了
You're scared.
好好享受吧
Enjoy.
好吧  听着
All right, all right.
《肖申克的救赎》是个好片
"Shawshank"'s a great flick,
但咱还是把淋浴场景跳过吧
but let's skip the shower scene, huh?
看看
Look --
早饭来了
Breakfast.
你对我哥干了什么
What did you do with my brother?
你马上就知道了
Oh, you'll find out.
这就送你一起上路
You're about to join him.
妈逼的食尸鬼
Frickin' hate ghouls!
迪恩
Dean?!
放开我  你个王八蛋
Let me go, you son of a bitch!
迪恩
Dean!
知道吗  你完全捅错地儿了
You know, you're sticking that thing in all the wrong places.
真的吗
Really?
你确实嚎叫来着嘛
You sure were squealing.
你随便吧
Knock yourself out.
这只是个寄宿用的身体
It's a host body.
一个希博伊根的女孩
Some girl from Sheboygan,
为了当演员  搬到了洛杉矶
moved to L.A. to be an actress.
这点小打小闹
It's probably not even the worst thing
对她来讲都不算最惨
that ever happened to her.
你笑什么
What are you laughing at?
迪恩·温彻斯特就在你身后
Dean Winchester's behind you...
大肉块
meatsack.
我们得走了
We should go.
你好呀  宝贝
Hello, sweetheart.
早上想跟我唠唠嗑不
Feeling chatty this morning, are we?
但愿是呢
Do hope so.
我可不想伤着你这漂亮脑袋上的一根毛
Wouldn't want to harm a hair on that pretty little head.
所以...
So...
你想跟我聊聊你爸了吗
You ready to tell me all about your daddy?
等会儿再聊
Hold that thought.
你现在该被食尸鬼啃了啊
You should be ghoul scat by now.
有意思吗
Really necessary?
这身衣服我可刚干洗过
I just had this dry-cleaned.
那...
So...
你们干嘛抓我
to what do I owe the reach-around?
克劳力
Crowley.
贱货
Whore.
好吧  随你怎么说
Okay, you know what?
真正的拷问专家从不会将手弄脏
The best torturers never get their hands dirty.
萨姆有话问你
Sam wants a word with you.
我能帮到你什么  萨姆
What can I do for you, Sam?
你明知故问
You know damn well.
我来要回我的灵魂
I want my soul back.
我觉得你好有种哦  萨姆
And here I thought you just grew some balls, Sam.
如何
Well?
-不行  -梅格
- No. - Meg?
我做不到
I can't.
做不到还是不愿意
Can't or won't.
我说了做不到
I said "Can't."
我没骗你  你个拖把头傻大个儿
And I meant can't, you mop-headed lumberjack.
把你拽出来已经算我走运了
I was lucky to get this much of you out.
要我再回那鬼地方  想都别想
Going back in there for the sloppy bits? No way.
我是没问题  可里面那两只呢
I'm good, but those two in there?
算了吧
Forget it.
-我怎么知道你有没有撒谎  -你是不知道
- How do I know you're not lying? - You don't.
但这也没差
But it doesn't change anything.
我告诉你
I'm telling you.
萨姆  你干嘛想要回来
Sam, why do you want the thing back?
路西法在牢笼里玩得可开心呢
Satan's got one juicy source of entertainment in there.
换作是我  要回那个灵魂
I'd swallow a rag off a bathhouse floor
还不如让我去吃屎
Before I took that soul.
除非你想把自己搞残掉
Unless you want to be a drooling mess.
萨姆  虽然我不想这么说  但他是对的
Sam, I hate to say it, but he's right.
好吧  我懂了  谢谢
Yeah, right. I get it. Thanks.
他归你处置了
He's all yours.
怎么  你疯了吗
Whoa. What are you, crazy?
他是我们唯一的希望
He's our only hope!
迪恩  你也听到他说的了
Dean, you heard him.
他没法帮我取回灵魂  他就没用了
He can't get it. He's useless!
你们会让我出来的对吧
You'll let me back out, right?
这一刀是为路西法的  你个自以为是的小...
This is for Lucifer, you pompous little --
感觉好多了
That's better.
你才不懂折磨的奥妙  你个小贱人
You don't know torture, you little insect.
放了他们
Leave them alone.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
一整季咱俩都没对手戏了
Haven't seen you all season.
你升职了呀
You the cavalry now?
把刀放下
Put the knife down.
你在上面也这么专横么
You that bossy in heaven?
听说你输给了拉斐尔
Hear you're losing out to Raphael.
这兄弟内斗搞得可真够激烈
The whole affair makes Vietnam look like a roller derby.
这礼品袋里装着什么
Hey, what's in the gift bag?
是你
You are.
不可能
Not possible.
你的骨头藏得可没那么好
You didn't hide your bones as well as you should have.
干得漂亮
Cookie for you.
你到底能不能弄回萨姆的灵魂
Can you restore Sam's soul or not?
如果我能在其他方面帮到你们...
If I can help out in any other --
回答他
Answer him!
我不能
I can't.
我不得不说  她很聪明
Well, she's smart. I'll give her that.
我本来也想连她一起干掉
I was gonna kill her, too.
当然  我会让你们先独处一会
'course, I'd have given you an hour with her first.
独处一会要做什么
Why would I want that?
谢谢  小卡
Thanks, Cass.
要不是你...
Hadn't have been for you...
克劳力说得没错
Crowley was right. It's not...
我在天上并不顺利
Going well for me upstairs.
-我们要是能帮上忙...  -你们帮不上
- If there's anything we can do... - There isn't.
我也不想事情发展成这样
I wish circumstances were different.
很多时候...
Much of the time...
我更愿意留在这
I'd rather be here.
小卡  我们知道你忙得焦头烂额
Look, Cass, we know you got a steaming pile on your plate.
你不需要道歉
There's no need for apologies.
我们是你的朋友
We're your friends.
听着  萨姆
Listen, Sam --
我们会另想办法
We'll find another way.
你真想要帮忙吗
You really want to help?
处理下那一屋子始祖吧
Prison full of monsters.
既不能丢下不管  也不能放了它们
Can't just leave 'em, can't let 'em go.
我明白
I understand.
他说得对
He's right, you know.
什么事
About?
关于你的灵魂
About your soul.
我们会找到办法
We'll figure something else out.
不  不可能
No, we won't.
为什么呢  就因为克劳力说...
Oh, why, because Crowley said --
克劳力说的你也听见了
You heard what Crowley said.
我也听到小卡说的了
And I heard what Cass said.
灵魂回到我的身体会将我撕成碎片
Putting this thing back in would smash me to bits.
-我们也不能确定  -知道吗
- We don't know that for sure. - You know what?
当天使和恶魔的意见达成共识
When angels and demons agree on something --
谁可能不上心呢
Call me nuts, I pay attention.
你现在才说吗
You say this now?
-我们差点为这破事死掉...  -没错
- After we practically died trying to -- - exactly.
我们差点就没命了
We almost got ourselves killed!
我们还要干多少次这种傻事
I mean, how many times do we risk our asses for this?
真是够了
Enough's enough.
-萨姆  -我不想要回灵魂了
- Sam -- - I don't think I want it back.
你都不知道自己在说些什么
You don't even know what you're saying.
我知道  我说的话你不爱听
No, I'm saying something you don't like.
你显然相当在意
You obviously care a lot.
但我想  我可能还是不要的好
But I think maybe I'm better off without it.
你错了
You're wrong.
-你简直大错特错  -我可不觉得
- You don't know how wrong you are. - I'm not sure about that.
萨姆  别走
Sam, don't walk away.
萨姆
Sam!
Sam!!